Total wala is in English
Hello Gas welcome to all of you in a new moto
blog so I am Sundar Album Tu My
Channel
and
[Music]
Honda Showroom and the
papers of Honda Showroom have to be updated that you all
know that I had to buy my Activa second hand
and we thought that
everything will be done by transferring it but I did
not know that the insurance name also has to be
transferred and so before that I had
tried to get Neha to get an intrinsic done
but the person who owned the car had taken
first party insurance so it will not be transferred for 5 years
and there will not be a new one also still
we are going
[Music]
If it happens then it is good and even better
[Laughter]
what is its procedure so after
looking at the location sometimes they are taking the car into
someone's field, sometimes they are taking it
into someone's shop, that is why
we left it, then one of my friends
said
that brother is here so I was about to
start from there in the fast block
but what happened was that my video
position was very bad, the phone was also switched off,
see all the police are standing there now we are about to cut it  It had
reduced for me, I did not even know that I had
not even done it, this is another family, let's
open it and see, it
expired 2 months ago
[Music]
and here
[Music] I
love Honda [
Music]
reply Kismat,
right now this area you are seeing, basically
means Rani will stay from here, you are
seeing brother, it must be my sister's mistake and I do
n't like my Activa very much, we are thinking
[Music]
see, I am facing a lot of problem, do you
know what is the problem with this helmet, I mean, for that
I will make a video with help,
for the motoglogging setup, right now I have to
run it less, but I will
tell my friends, brother, please arrange something with
me, the phone motor
[Music]
[Music] has
not been done, let's go
to this uncle
[Music] I
said this, brother,
how is your life going, I want to
tell you something last night,
she is in girls college right now, she is a girl, brother, I had
repaired it for a few days
[Music] from
here, we will go a little far away from here and
call from girls college, we will say that
if you can come then come, he was saying that  He has a
class from 12:00, I do
n't know whether he has a class or not
[Music]
We will stop the car here and my
friends will call and say, hey go brother,
why are you taking my time brother, if you do
n't want to receive calls then
no problem, let's end it here, bye bye